so let's discuss the answer to our
laptop falls down quiz
for the pavement the failure is whatever
causes the pavement to no longer perform
its function properly
here
you might be tempted to say that it
needs to be replaced is the failure but
actually that's the repair of the
failure this is fixing the pavement it's
not something that causes it to deviate
from its function
really it breaking
caused it to need to be replaced so
breaking
is the failure
what's the fault it's the event
that resulted in the first error in this
case it's not that the laptop fell out
of the bag it had nothing to do with the
pavement
it is that the laptop hits the pavement
and now what was the first error well it
was that the pavement developed a crack
the structure the internal behavior of
the pavement is no longer the same as
the proper pavement
but we really noticed this in terms of
deviating from its specified function
when it broke
so we can still use a pavement with a
crack the crack expanded so the error
became
bigger
but really until it broke the pavement
was functioning properly so this is
what we get at the end